(Howard:)is going out of our way
to criticize each other.
(Howard:)Although, there are ways
to improve our communication.
(Howard:)One thing I learned when
I was in couples therapy was...
(Bernadette:)Who were you
(Bernadette:)in couples therapy with?
(Howard:)Not important.
(Bernadette:)Was it your mom?
(Bernadette:)It was your mom.
(Howard:)Anyway, the therapist had us
tell each other
(Howard:)what we loved about one another.
Oh, that's so sweet!
(Bernadette:)I want to do that.
(Amy:)All right.
(Bernadette:)Okay, um...
(Bernadette:)I love that you make me laugh.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Howard:)And I love that you're strong
and independent.
(Bernadette:)And yet, I still love
when you hold a door for me.
(Howard:)I love that I'm kind of a slob
around here, and...
(laughing):
you're okay with that.
(Bernadette:)Uh-huh.
(Bernadette:)And I love that I work
and do all the cleaning,